Not if. When.
A House of Dynamite is a thriller film directed by Kathryn Bigelow.
When a single, unattributed missile is launched at the United States, a race
begins to determine who is responsible and how to respond.
POTUS, played by Idris Elba.
Captain Olivia Walker, played by Rebecca Ferguson.
Deputy National Security Advisor Jake Baerington, played by Gabriel Basso.
Secretary of Defense Reid Baker, played by Jared Harris.
General Anthony Brady, played by Tracy Letts.
Major Daniel Gonzalez, played by Anthony Ramos.
A House of Dynamite is a 2025 American political thriller film
directed by Kathryn Bigelow and written by Noah Oppenheim.
It stars Idris Elba, Rebecca Ferguson, Gabriel
Basso, Jared Harris, and Tracy Letts.
The film shows the perspectives and responses of different U.S.
government and military officials after an unknown adversary
launches an intercontinental ballistic missile at Chicago.
A House of Dynamite premiered in the main competition of the 82nd Venice International Film
Festival on September 2, 2025, where it was nominated for the Golden Lion.
It had a limited theatrical release in the UK on October 3 and was released in the United
States on October 10, before its global streaming debut on Netflix on October 24.
It generally received positive reviews.
The film explores themes of the white house, woman
director, detached, political thriller, ironic.
The tone is intense.